Guide to the New York State milk strike records, 1941-1961.
New York State milk strike records, 1941-1961
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State milk strike records, 1941-1961.
6628
Federal Milk Market Administrator (U.S.).Northeast area.
.5 cubic ft.
Telegrams, maps, memos
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes western union telegrams as well as correspondence, newspapers clippings, and a letter to New York City Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia concerning the pending July 1941 milk strike.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes western union telegrams as well as correspondence, newspapers clippings, and a letter to New York City Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia concerning the pending July 1941 milk strike.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Federal Milk Market Administrator (U.S.).; LaGuardia, Fiorello H.(Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947.
Subjects:
Dairying--Economic aspects.; Agriculture and politics.; Dairy laws--New York (State); Strikes and lockouts--United States.; Milk trade--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
1.5\aPhysical location: Box 1:Milk strike records
CONTAINER LIST
- NYS Milk Strike, July 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NYS Milk Strike, October 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NYS Milk Strike-Data, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NYS Milk Strike-Telegrams, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NYS Milk Strike-Telegrams, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NYS Milk Strike, February 25, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NYS Milk Strike, February 26, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NYS Milk Strike, February 27, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NYS Milk Strike, February 28, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NYS Milk Strike,1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NYS Milk Strike, March 2, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NYS Milk Strike, March 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- NYS Milk Strike, March 4, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- NYS Milk Strike-Telegrams, March 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NYS Milk Strike-Maps (Box 1, Folder 15)
- NYS Milk Strike, October 1961 and October 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)